[Music]
i didn't think i'd share a video with
you this week because i was feeling
quite lacking in creative energy
but as i traveled west and the bear
mountains and rugged canyons turned into
the lush forests and beaches of the
washington peninsula i felt different
the skies were blue and had a sweet wet
scent
i felt a spark of inspiration to travel
freely and experience the natural world
again
i also got to share this trip with my
boyfriend we've never taken a trip
together and it was a very special time
for us
it got me thinking about my past self
and how my life has changed
[Music]
loneliness is a feeling i struggled with
for years as many of us do
i've found it isn't always a feeling
dependent on whether or not you have a
lot of friends or an active social life
it's about your relationship with
yourself
about fearing being alone with your own
thoughts and yet feeling lonely because
you do not have a deep connection with
yourself and others
i think most everyone feels different at
some point in their lives
for a lot of us this happens during our
younger years
these are times when we're discovering
who we are and it's natural that we feel
like we cannot relate to a vast majority
of people
but it makes us feel alone like we don't
belong
yet the mere fact that this is such a
common feeling shows us that that isn't
always true
there are thousands of books and videos
and testaments all about this feeling of
otherness
it is proof that we have so much more in
common with each other than not at any
given point
for example i've never been able to
handle more than a couple close
friendships at a time and i'm quickly
overwhelmed after several days of a lot
of socializing
it used to make me feel like something
was wrong
but now i know that many people are
introverted like myself it's very common
over time i've found people that value
me and hold my trust
but in my case those relationships took
many many years to build
to be clear i have no doubt each and
every one of us has a truly unique light
that wants to shine ever brighter as we
grow and love for ourselves
we have an individual imprint but we are
also more connected to others than not
i've come to see it as a responsibility
to interact with my world with an open
heart to accept others assuming we share
common ground
it has helped me feel far less lonely
and encouraged me to connect and to give
[Music]
a very practical way i combated
loneliness was by investing time in
myself and my hobbies but also by
accepting that every emotion is an
opportunity i also let go of my pride
and admitted to myself that in my case i
wanted to live my life near my family in
typical hispanic culture i was raised
with a sense of constant togetherness
i miss that living alone in the city and
even though i was teased at times for
wanting to be near my parents it's what
i knew would make me happier and less
lonely
i've lived my own individual life and
made my own decisions while still living
near my family and that worked for me
i'm no less of an adult of course and
i'm happier because of that decision
through that i realized how important it
is to know your own heart instead of
mindlessly adhering to what your society
dictates is the definition of success
and true independence
i can certainly say that i still feel
lonely from time to time i think for
some of us it's a natural occurrence
but i don't see that loneliness as
negative
if anything it reminds me to value my
spirituality and to not take for granted
the blessings in my life
whoever you are and whatever chapter you
are in your life i hope that you can
continue to embrace the story and know
that we're always evolving and that who
you will be tomorrow is not yet known
[Music]
distracted
thank you all for your lovely words in
my last video i recently got a call from
my brother saying that we finally have
blue skies again
it may only be temporary but it is so
exciting and a great reminder that
no matter how dark things get the light
will always come back
it's just a matter of time
i will share more of my trip next week
so far it has been wonderful to get away
from everything and i'm sending you my
love have a wonderful day or night
[Music]
you